* Website Privacy

Website Privacy Policy
======================

Disclaimer
----------

Washburn University School of Law ('Washburn Law') maintains its web site, washburnlaw.edu, on a continuing basis. However, Washburn Law does not represent, guarantee, or warrant that all information provided is accurate, complete, current, or suitable for the user's purposes. Washburn Law specifically disclaims any and all liability for claims or damages that may result from its web site or information contained therein, including any web sites maintained by third parties and linked to Washburn Law web sites, for which responsibility lies with the entity providing the information. A link from a Washburn Law web site in no way implies authorization or endorsement of that site by Washburn University School of Law.

Information Collected By Washburn Law
-------------------------------------

Washburn Law is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy. As part of the operation of washburnlaw.edu, we gather certain types of information about our users. We would like to explain the types of information we gather and what we do with it.

Washburn Law collects two types of identifying information from users: personal data that users supply to us voluntarily (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregated data (such as information about traffic patterns on washburnlaw.edu).

Personal Data
-------------

Personal data is collected when users voluntarily provide data to Washburn Law through one of the web site forms, such as when requesting [admissions information](https://www.washburnlaw.edu/admissions/getpacket/index.php "Go the the request an admissions packet form."), or by directly sending an email to a Washburn Law employee or department. Your information from these forms will be used to execute the immediate transaction, and will be provided to other parties only as necessary to complete your transaction. In addition, we may store your information locally in order to facilitate contact with you in the future. Note that in some instances you will not be able to submit a form unless you are willing to provide all requested information. Washburn Law will not provide any of your personal information to third parties without your permission, unless compelled by law or court order to do so, and will not sell any personal information to third parties for purposes of marketing, advertising, or promotion.

Aggregated Information
----------------------

When you visit washburnlaw.edu, we collect certain types of information that does not identify individual users. This information is aggregated with hundreds of thousands of other pieces of information to create summary statistics that help us determine which information is of most interest to users, to improve the web site, to identify system problem areas, to carry out other administrative tasks, or to help determine technical requirements.

Information collected includes:

* Hostname: the hostname, site name, username, and IP address of the computer requesting access to the site.
* User-Agent: the type of browser, its version, and the operating system of the computer requesting access (e.g., Netscape 4 for Windows, IE 4 for Macintosh, etc.).
* Referrer: the web page the user came from.
* System date: the date and time on the server at the time of access.
* Full request: the exact request the user made.
* Status: the status code the server returned, e.g., fulfilled request, file not found, etc.
* Content length: the size, in bytes, of the file sent to the user.
* Method: the request method used by the browser (e.g., post, get).
* Universal Resource Identifier (URI): the location of the particular resource requested. (More commonly known as a URL.)
* Query string of the URI: anything after a question mark in a URI. For example, if a keyword search has been requested, the search word will appear in the query string.
* Protocol: the technical protocol and version used, i.e., http 1.0, ftp, etc.

The above information is not used in any way that would reveal personally identifying information to outside parties unless Washburn Law is legally required to do so.

Cookies
-------

washburnlaw.edu does not use cookies to keep track of users or their sessions.

Security
--------

We use standard security measures to protect any personal information that you may provide to us. However, we cannot guarantee that your submissions to our website, any content residing on our servers, or any transmissions from our server will be completely secure. While no system can provide guaranteed security, we take reasonable efforts to keep information you provide to us secure, and physical security at the location of the server where information is stored.

Miscellaneous
-------------

By using washburnlaw.edu, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Washburn Law as described in this policy.

Washburn Law fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to release information about users who we believe are in violation of our content guidelines. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful.

Washburn Law wants you to be aware that when you click on links that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the internet, Washburn Law cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties.

Your Consent
------------

By using washburnlaw.edu, you consent to the collection and use of personal and aggregate information by Washburn Law as outlined in this privacy policy. Washburn Law reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
